The next guest is Tony Zhou, an art director from NetEase.
He is also a member of the Destiny Rising production team, which is about to launch NetEase games.
He will bring us the valuable experience of using Marvel's Titan in the actual game project.
Welcome, Tony!
Good afternoon, everyone.
I am very happy and honored to attend this user conference.
In the beginning, Tony and Terry shared with you a lot about Marvel's actual game content.
Today, I would like to share with you some of the examples of projects in NetEase.
I would like to share with you some of the examples of projects in NetEase.
Thank you.
First of all, I would like to introduce our project.
This project was launched in November last year.
It is officially named as Destiny Rising.
It is an IP mobile game for Destiny.
It is a game that allows users to authorize IPs, and to search for images.
NetEase is developing it independently.
Basically, it is a complete process of Destiny.
The background is also a world view.
We'll start with a coverage clip from last year.
Let's take a look at the video we watched in Flash.
This is what we saw over the last year's Naon Live.
Let's start with the clip.
This is a clip from the end of the year.
We are about to take a look at the practice of the game.
© transcript Emily Beynon
Even though there are 30 images, some of the characters move and there are some changes or bugs in the equipment.
This can be verified in advance.
Then from the perspective of the product, the corresponding character plan can run to this game in advance.
Although it is only a blur, it can verify some of the design movements, including the special effects of the skill, etc.
Because it is a design game, we are also doing some gun development.
In the process of gun development, we also use this process.
For example, if we develop a G10 million or a G10 million,
we will verify in advance whether its opening and closing state or trigger structure is reasonable at the whiteboard stage.
I think this whiteboard process is very good.
It is also a recognition of the Bungie team.
The next thing I want to introduce is the actual development of the project.
The first thing is that it can help us designers to quickly improve the design efficiency.
Because it has a quick implementation effect and function.
The second thing is that it can help us evaluate the design plan through this more intuitive effect and quickly adjust it.
The second thing is that it can greatly reduce the cost of development.
Then,
we can improve the production efficiency.
These two things will be discussed later.
First of all, this is an example of our quick implementation effect.
From the left to the middle, on the far right is a low poly.
In the middle is a model of MD.
The last one is a high mode production.
This is actually a MP3 that we developed when the game was launched in the late middle of the year.
This is an MP3 character.
The problem was that we didn't have enough cost to start making it from the original part.
So we had a meeting with the designers.
We brought it directly from the 3D production team.
Then we started to customize it according to their needs.
On the left is a simple model of MD that we put on the Z20.
Then, through the product development process, including the MP3, we started to make it.
Finally, we went to the Z20 on the far right and finished the high mode.
The whole process took about 7-8 days.
From the left to the right.
This time includes the meeting and the meeting.
Actually, it's very fast.
If you are making it from the original part, it will take about half a month.
Because the original part is more refined.
So these are all for its powerful extension function.
The second thing is that last year I made a work of my own.
I wanted to combine the image of a Chinese woman and cyberpunk.
During this process, I also did a lot of research on the project.
For example, on the left, there are some Dongmao images.
Or this kind of vest image.
I think that Muppet Designer can really help these people like me.
People like me who don't have the power to design.
Because it can solve this problem.
And it can help us to understand and optimize it better.
The second thing is that this software can actually help us save costs.
I believe this is the most mentioned word.
Especially when it comes to the reduction of cost.
This word is actually a bit of an exaggeration.
For example, in the Resonate project, we established an MDT warehouse.
We accumulated a lot of high-quality clothing assets.
Including the copyright information.
We also did the classification.
Including the top and bottom clothes.
And the accessories, including the backpack.
All of these have been refined.
And for the new characters, if there is a similar kind of clothing.
We can use it to modify it.
We have calculated that.
After the MDT warehouse was established.
And before that.
The development time for the team was reduced by about 30% to 50%.
The three pictures below.
In fact, these are the designs of the three different characters in our project.
In fact, the overall design is not much different.
It's all from the bottom to the bottom.
It's a two-sided design.
The top is all cloth.
When we were making it.
We used the same kind of clothing.
We just made some changes in the details.
In fact, it's a very big time saving.
Then MDT in the project.
The last landing.
What questions do we need to pay attention to?
In fact, we pay more attention to the length of the fabric in the game.
Because in the end, in the game.
The length of the fabric will directly affect.
The visual effect of the game.
And some performance problems.
I'm here.
Just a few points.
First of all, the first one is to pay attention to the performance of the screentone.
Because.
After all, this is a mobile experience.
So.
When designing.
We will pay attention to the screentone of the character.
And then.
In the end.
This 3D production environment.
To emphasize this kind of wide-ranging performance.
Because it can be more practical in the game.
More visual impact.
So sometimes in the design.
We find.
In many places.
Screentone is not very good.
Our 3D production.
3D production will be self-explanatory.
To adjust things like this.
The second is.
As much as possible.
To open up the different material characteristics in the object.
In fact.
There is a simple example on the picture.
We see.
That is to say.
There are.
Bags.
Backpacks.
And then.
T-shirts.
And some pants.
Such movements.
In addition.
We are in.
Zbrush.
To do some.
Structural additions.
In the simulation of MD.
In fact.
We will also.
Pay more attention to.
To open up this material.
Because.
This is also.
To enrich the performance of the character.
Increase.
A real.
Idea.
And then.
This is a multi-layer.
The layer.
The layers.
That is.
The interweaving of layers.
In fact.
The senior.
Also said.
That is to say.
When we are doing.
The material.
No matter in.
The interior.
Or the external.
The public.
All will.
Sometimes.
The production.
Will be limited.
It is.
The materials.
Do.
Very nice.
A lot of details.
It will be limited.
In fact.
When we are.
This kind of too fine material is not suitable for the overall performance of the character.
The right side is actually a process of joints and materials.
After all, we play games on A-Pose or T-Pose.
So when we are making the material, we should pay attention to the joints or the joints on both sides.
We will pay more attention to the details and performance of it when we are modeling.
Because many times we find that when we are making the model, the material is very beautiful.
But in the final binding, due to the movement of the joints, sometimes the character is very large.
So there will be some stretching, which makes the character look strange.
Finally, to summarize, what are the advantages of MD for this project?
First of all, it promotes creativity.
It has a very clean environment.
And the practical feedback can encourage designers to try more creative solutions.
From the moment I first came into contact with MD, I felt that MD was just helping us to deal with high-end games and models at the beginning.
But now, with MD's progress and return, it will start to be used in design.
We started to go to MD for design.
I think this is a very important change.
The second is high-end fabric simulation.
In fact, this should be MD's advantage from the beginning to the present.
Traditional modeling requires a very strong software and professional knowledge.
But with MD, there is some basic knowledge of art, including the learning of the software.
In fact, many artists can start to try to do some clothing design and fabric production.
This is very good.
The third is the short production cycle.
This is not so difficult.
I think the emergence of MD, especially in production,
will greatly speed up our work process and improve the work efficiency of our artists.
And if there are some overlaps in the middle, the cost will be much lower than before.
So let me summarize.
The core value of MD is that it allows game designers to create more, have more freedom, have a higher degree of creativity,
and have a lower cost of development.
Thank you.
That's all I want to share with you today.
And then I want to talk about something else.
I think in the past few years, with the rise of AI, the game industry has made a lot of progress.
From the beginning of Rising to now, there have been some twists and turns in the middle.
I almost can't meet you all.
But in the end, it's all done.
I think confidence is actually very important to the individual and the team.
It will determine the direction of our work.
It will determine our judgment.
So I still hope that everyone will not be influenced by the atmosphere of this kind of exchange.
And then just do what you like.
And then in the end, I still want to thank the host for being able to create such a good exchange platform today.
And let us communicate with each other.
And then I also hope that all the artists here today will be able to make a better work of art.
Thank you all.
If you are interested in this project, you can also ask questions.
And then I don't know if there are any fans of fate today.
This project, in fact, we received a lot of feedback from players.
It's still very good.
But we also learned through this kind of overseas test.
In fact, European and American people playing games are not the same as us.
They are not very able to accept mobile games.
It's not because they think mobile games are very low.
It's because they don't want to be in the wrong pot.
They like to receive PC or receive large-scale games.
Because after all, their way of playing games is mostly to do this kind of mainstream.
So we are now also trying to optimize the PC version.
And then if you are interested, there will be an overseas test in the first half of this year.
And then there will also be more information about this game at the 520 gaming conference on the Internet.
Well, that's it.